paidweeklyguaranteed.com 2013-11-26

# Privacy Policy

**Warning** : mysql_select_db() expects parameter 2 to be resource, boolean given in **/home/paidweek/public_html/legal/privacy.php** on line **3**

Effective February 2013

## Privacy Notice Table Of Contents:

Our Commitment To Privacy

The Information We Collect

The Information We DONT Collect

How We Use Information

Our Commitment To Data Security

Our Commitment To Children's Privacy

## Our Commitment To Privacy:

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

## The Information We Collect:

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on this website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: Name Address Email address Phone number

## The Information We DONT Collect:

Credit/Debit Card Information

## The Way We Use Information:

We use the information you provide about yourself when requesting information only to complete that information request. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete the neccessary information request. We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.

You can register with our website if you would like to receive our blog updates as well as updates on our new products and services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form. We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

## Our Commitment To Data Security:

To prevent unauthorised access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

## Our Commitment To Children's Privacy:

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 18, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 18.
